Hi Gas, I am Kunal Rajput and you are watching
my channel So Gas,
I have brought important information for you again
which is related to two wheeler insurance,
like in the previous video, in
my Guddi Insurance, I
told you how useless it is to take insurance
if you are going to take digital insurance
because see, if you have any
issue or accident, you go to make a claim, then
if you are already
worried because of the exchange, your car has got
damaged and sometimes we
also get hurt, then we get worried,
in that situation, if an insurance company for
which we have taken insurance for
our help, also
troubles you, then my friend, our pain gets
doubled, okay Gas, so
this experience happened with me, so
I thought I would share it with you people and
I shared it with you people and let's move ahead, I
just
want to give more information, if you do not get insurance, then if it is a
new car, then it
gets a separate insurance and when your car is more than 5 years
old, then the rules are in place now
According to that, as far as I know, there is an
option of zero, okay, if you
take that, then you must ask this, those
brothers who do not know, okay, they must ask what is
zero type, what is there in the gas, it is
also possible that they have
different terms and conditions, every company may have
different, but as far as I have heard,
you get full tax if you have zero
deferment, okay, under two wheeler insurance
or if you are also doing your car insurance,
okay, then in that you get
full tax under zero type, you get full tax,
rest of the terms and conditions, still they will definitely
ask, it is for the first 5 years, I would
like to tell you, when you buy a new vehicle, then
they tell you that friend,
I am insuring your entire vehicle, friend,
this is that, they will
ask them, brother, what type of insurance are you giving, are you
giving only third party, third
party means that you will be back from the challan,
okay, and if you cause
damage to someone else with your vehicle, it is
not that you will be back only from the challan
People will be saved a lot from this, the thing is that you are
saved from the challan only, no, gas is
not saved from the challan only, it is for your safety, that is why the
government has made such a rule
that you should take insurance, the reason for this is that it is done for
running, the rest it is for
your personal purpose only because if
your vehicle causes damage
to someone and he dies, I am sorry that such a thing should
not happen to anyone, but I would
like to tell you, it is important to tell you, okay, if something like this happens
in an accident, then if you have third
part insurance, then
you get a claim of up to 1 lakh from that insurance,
okay, maximum, and if someone dies, then
that code decides what will be given to him as
compensation, so this is
important information related to insurance, that is why
I am giving you this information
because previously I had
posted a video in the group of mare exchanges
and some questions had come from people like
related to cashless, in the group of cashless,
I also know that the meaning of cashless is this much,
see if zero  If it's in depth, then your
cashless means that
you won't have to pay any money. Whatever expenses are incurred,
you won't have to pay anything. Get your vehicle
repaired and bring it home. Okay, but if
your vehicle isn't covered under your zero policy, or
your insurance isn't covered, then the
insurance company will deduct the money you have to pay
from there, and
you'll have to pay the remaining amount. Okay, so
they say cashless, meaning that you don't have to pay the full amount,
whereas this word shouldn't be used.
Cashless means that you do
n't have to pay anything.
Cashless has its own meanings for gas, I'll
explain them, and I'd like to tell you that you should
n't take digital insurance at all.
If anyone sees this, I'm
sharing my experience, and I
share this experience because I've already suffered this.
I don't want
anything to happen to you.
YouTube is a very good medium through which you can
help someone. By creating a video,
if you think my video is useful,
please do so for me.  I will do this much that you
subscribe to the channel, the
more you share the video the better it is
for the people, everyone will be saved from loss, so
listen to the one who does it, if you don't know then he will confirm that if the
insurance is being given to
you, when you are buying a new car, if it has
zero depth, then what are the taxes
in the third party, I have already told you
what taxes are there, now let's go to the
insurance related to the car, so
gas, even now my insurance is
digital, that is pending because I have my
own terms and conditions, I am paying it,
he is at his place, the person who
does the survey, in the rules the rule is
that he has to come, he will collect all the photos,
whereas he did not come, still I went myself to
their cashless center, friend,
actually look, I would like to tell you that my
vehicle is my wife's,
I have bought it for my wife, I cannot
drive because I am handicapped, so
I cannot type, so I have bought it
for my wife, okay, so friend, their
Cashless centers are present at so many places, if
this is the condition of one cashless center, then
where will the others be, if you leave your car there, there is no
place to come back,
neither are there any autos nor anything, or
their guy says that we will drop you, at least
you take your auto, take the bus
and go from there, we will drop the
car there, they are not even telling
how many days it will take to repair, whereas it is less than 2
hours, only
okay, I got it done once before also, it does
not take more than 2 hours, you
leave the car there, I don't even know the timing, but
how can you leave the car like this in a cashless center, sorry, it is such a
small shop, it is a Hero service center, the
authorized one they have taken, it is for
digital, okay, so
brother, how can you leave it there, if you take a small one, there will be no
problem with this thing,
you will park my car outside, you will not park it inside, so
brother, this is happening, the surveyor is
still conducting the survey, it has been a
month to two and a half, so this
kind of friend, there is rain and such things
These people ask you, tell me friend, when you have an
accident and you are making a claim immediately,
many times you do
n't even know the process of making a claim, because of this process
people don't even file an action,
everyone thinks that I am taking
insurance so that I do
n't get a challan, whereas
in your insurance, if you know everything, if you know the
claim process, then you
definitely benefit and insurance is taken for this thing,
gas is fine, so I would like to
suggest you that do not take digital
insurance at all and
I also wanted to give you the information related to insurance through this video,
which I have given you till now, so hope
you people must have understood, if you have any other
questions, then whatever information I have in this section, related to two
wheeler insurance,
whatever information related to insurance,
I do not have that much knowledge in the section of insurance,
but if you ask, I will
definitely tell you by searching, okay,
I have done business in two line insurance, that's why
I know, so I told you how it happens
in that section and a Bajaj
Allians  There is insurance for gas, that too is very
conditional, I have spent a lot on it, so
I know I have been cheated,
look I am entering from a mare, but
I have reduced it, so their friend is also the same,
okay, the rest I would like to tell you,
do not take insurance for gas, you will
regret it a lot, I am still getting worried
and I am not taking it seriously
because right now, friend, whatever the situation is,
okay, according to that, he should reduce it,
he is not doing it, okay, they have
made a wrong estimate and given it to me, which is
not correct at all, it is not as I am seeing, the
thing that is broken, they are thinking according to their own will that it should be like this, it should be like that,
okay, so that's all I was going to
tell you, do
not waste your money and take care of the
information I have given you related to insurance, take
care, get it
insured properly and
insurance is taken
for the benefit and you should take advantage of those benefits, take
insurance from them,
I do not fancy it  These people
will trouble you a lot, don't worry,
take that insurance which will be butter for you, I would
like to suggest insurance from my side, the
rest is your choice, I had a very
good experience last time,
I said yes to them for the settlement amount,
they settled it immediately,
everything was done within 2-3 days, okay,
my experience with gas was very good, as soon as
it gets over, I am going to get it done,
I liked it a lot,
okay gas, this much in the video has become quite long, if
you like the information, then
as I said, please friend, definitely share it,
my message should reach the people and they should also
benefit, bye